Guide to the Jean Kilbourne Papers, 1918-2014 and undated RL.10982
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Research Files, 1948-2003 and undated; 34 boxes
  - Feminism--Dysfunctional familes (IP Stiver), 1989 (Box 32)
  - Feminism--Education--Children, 1971-1992 (Box 32)
  - Feminism--Education--Faculty, 1978-1981 (Box 32)
  - Feminism--Education--General, 1981-1992 (Box 32)
  - Feminism--Education--Higher education, 1978-1990 (Box 32)
  - Feminism--Education--Science and math, 1977-1989 (Box 32)
  - Feminism--Feeling Like a Fraud (Peggy McIntosh), 1985 (Box 33)
  - Feminism--Feminist theory, 1970-1994; 2 folders (Box 33)
  - Feminism--History, 1969 and undated (Box 33)
  - Feminism--Humor, 1980-1990 (Box 33)
  - Feminism--Language, 1971-1993 (Box 33)
  - Feminism--Opposition and criticism, 1976-1980 (Box 33)
  - Feminism--Pamphlets and miscellaneous, 1971-1978 (Box 33)
  - Feminism--Patriarchy, 1971-1978 (Box 33)
  - Feminism--Power and powerlessness, 1978-1991 (Box 33)
  - Feminism--Psychology, 1977-1991 (Box 33)
  - Feminism--Religion, 1959-1980 (Box 33)
  - Feminism--Self-in-relation, 1980-1993 (Box 34)
  - Feminism--Sex differences, 1978-1997 (Box 34)
  - Feminism--Sex role socialization, 1971-1994 (Box 34)
  - Feminism--Socialism and women's issues, 1979 (Box 34)
  - Feminism--Stereotypes, 1976-1979 (Box 34)
  - Feminism--Wellesley publications, 1977-2000 (Box 34)
  - Feminism--Women's movement, 1978-1985 (Box 34)
  - Global marketing, 1979-1990 (Box 34)
  - Global marketing--Asia, 1979-1986 (Box 34)
  - Global marketing--Latin America, 1982 (Box 34)
  - Global marketing--Social marketing, 1980-1983 (Box 35)
  - Greed, 1980-1992 (Box 35)
  - Health--General, 1980-1991 (Box 35)
  - Health--Illness and disease, 1979-1997 (Box 35)
  - Individual as solution, 1985-1991 (Box 35)
  - Individual vs. conformity, 1985-1994 (Box 35)
  - Junk food, 1980-1991 (Box 35)
  - Market research, 1979-1982 (Box 35)
  - Market research--Psychographics, 1980-1985 (Box 35)
  - Market research--Psychological, 1977-1989 (Box 35)
  - Market research--Techniques, 1979-1997 (Box 35)
  - Marketing--The "New Man" (male homemakers, etc.), 1980-1985 (Box 35)
  - Marketing to women--The "New Woman", 1970-1988; 2 folders (Box 35)
  - Marketing to women--Traditional, 1966-1971 (Box 35)
  - Marketing to women--Women as consumers, 1966-1978 (Box 35)
  - Marketing to women--Women's magazines, 1974-1982 (Box 35)
  - Marketing to women--Working women, 1976-1979 (Box 35)
  - Media, 1978-1989 (Box 35)
  - Media and politics, 1981-1988 (Box 35)
  - Men--And feminism, 1977-1983 (Box 35)
  - Men--Clippings, 1979-1986 (Box 35)
  - Men--Intimacy, 1975-1986 (Box 35)
  - Men--Machismo, 1977-1982 (Box 35)
  - Men--Men's liberation, 1970-1992 (Box 36)
  - Men--Resources, 1977-1991 (Box 36)
  - Mental health, 1979-1984 (Box 36)
  - Mental health--Depression and suicide, 1979-1993 (Box 36)
  - Mental health--Spirituality, 1979-1981 (Box 36)
  - Mental health--Stress and anxiety, 1979-1988 (Box 36)
  - Mental health--Therapy, 1971-1979 (Box 36)
  - News/Coverage, 1977-1991 (Box 36)
  - Outdoor advertising, 1980-1991 (Box 36)
  - Pornography--Censorship, 1977-1993 (Box 36)
  - Pornography--Child pornograhy/Child actors, 1977-1983 (Box 36)
  - Pornography--Domestic violence, 1991 and undated (Box 36)
  - Pornography--Feminist theory, 1979-1986 (Box 36)
  - Pornography--General, 1976-1994 (Box 36)
  - Pornography--Industry, 1979-1980 (Box 36)
  - Pornography--Research, 1978-2000 (Box 37)
  - Pornography--Women Against Pornography, undated (Box 37)
  - Racism--Advertising and media, 1979-1994 (Box 37)
  - Racism--Facing History and Ourselves, 1993-1994 (Box 37)
  - Racism--General, 1966-1990 (Box 37)
  - Racism--Women, 1974-1985 (Box 37)
  - Relationships--Friends, 1979-1986 (Box 37)
  - Relationships--Jealousy, undated (Box 37)
  - Relationships--Lesbians, 1973-1981 (Box 37)
  - Relationships--Love/Lovers, 1975-1980 (Box 37)
  - Relationships--Male homosexuality, 1978-1980 (Box 37)
  - Research--Magazines, 1973-1988 (Box 37)
  - Research--Magazines (includes "Images of Women in Vogue" by Gillian Caldwell), 1973-1988 (Box 38)
  - Right wing/Religion, 1980-1981 (Box 38)
  - Selling violence against women, 1977-1992 (Box 38)
  - Sex and violence, 1980-1993 (Box 38)
  - Sex in the media, 1977-1988 (Box 38)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Advertisers' responses, 1977-1992 (Box 38)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Advertising, 1974-1995 (Box 38)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Aging--Elderly, 1980-1998 (Box 38)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Aging--Media images, 1980-1998 (Box 38)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Aging--Older women, 1970-1994 (Box 38)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Beauty--Beauty product hazards, 1970-1987 (Box 39)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Beauty--Beauty products, 1980-1986 (Box 39)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Beauty--Beauty products for men, 1979-1984 (Box 39)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Beauty--Contests, 1980-1989 (Box 39)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Beauty--Cosmetic surgery, 1977-1991 (Box 39)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Beauty--Cosmetics, 1969-1983 (Box 39)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Beauty--Fashion, 1969-1993 (Box 39)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Beauty--Feminine hygiene, 1978-1982 (Box 39)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Beauty--General, 1980-1996 (Box 39)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Beauty--Ideal image, 1979-1997; 3 folders (Box 39)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Body image--Large women, 1979-1988 (Box 39)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Body image--Media, 1984-1995 (Box 40)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Body image--Research, 1979-1996 (Box 40)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Canada, 1984-1985 (Box 40)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Children and advertising, 1983-1998 (Box 40)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Children's television, 1973-1990 (Box 40)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Cross-cultural, 1973-1991 (Box 40)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Dieting, 1983-1997 (Box 40)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Dieting and self image, 1983-1995 (Box 40)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Eating disorders--Anorexia, 1981-1988 (Box 40)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Eating disorders Awareness and Prevention (EDAP), 1996 (Box 40)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Eating disorders--Bulimia, 1981-1988 (Box 40)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Eating disorders--Food addiction, 1983 and undated (Box 40)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Eating disorders--General, 1984-1996 and undated (Box 41)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Eating disorders--Men, 1984 (Box 41)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Eating disorders--Obesity, 1979-2000 (Box 41)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Eating disorders--Substance abuse, 1991-1997 (Box 41)
  - Sex role stereotypes--"Fatism" and weight prejudice, 1982-1997 (Box 41)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Food and hunger, 1985 and undated (Box 41)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Magazines, 1976-1993 (Box 41)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Male sex objects, 1978-1989 (Box 41)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Media, 1976-1995 (Box 41)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Men, 1979-1994 (Box 41)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Midlife, 1980 and undated (Box 41)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Obsession with thinness, 1984-1995 (Box 41)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Research, 1973-1997; 2 folders (Box 42)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Television, 1970-1991 (Box 42)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Toys, 1977-1997 (Box 42)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Achievement, 1991 and undated (Box 42)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Child care, 1980-1994 (Box 42)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Comparable worth, 1980-1985 (Box 42)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Displaced homemakers, 1980 (Box 42)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Divorce, 1986 (Box 42)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Families, 1979-1990 (Box 42)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Fatherhood, 1980-1990 (Box 42)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--General, 1986-1990 (Box 42)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Housewives, 1977 and undated (Box 42)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Housework, 1977-1979 (Box 42)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Marriage, 1979-1983 (Box 42)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Motherhood, 1976-1990 (Box 42)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Mothers and daughters, 1978-1982 (Box 43)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Professional women, 1979-1986 (Box 43)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Re-entry, 1969-1981 (Box 43)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Research, 1976-1990 (Box 43)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Widowhood, 1977 (Box 43)
  - Sex role stereotypes--Women and work--Working mothers, 1976-1993 (Box 43)
  - Sexism and media--Children's literature, 1970 and undated (Box 43)
  - Sexism and media--Films, 1979-1985 (Box 43)
  - Sexism and media--Jokes, cartoons, etc., 1948-1987 and undated (Box 43)
  - Sexism and media--Music video, 1984-1993 (Box 43)
  - Sexism and media--Popular culture, 1975-1983 (Box 43)
  - Sexism and media--Sex role stereotyping--Children's television commercials, 1975-1976 (Box 43)
  - Sexism and media--Sex role stereotyping--Television commercials--effects (Box 43)
  - Sexism and media--Sex role stereotyping--Television commercials--General, 1967-1980 (Box 44)
  - Sexism and media--Sex role stereotyping--Television commercials--Research, 1972-1988 (Box 44)
  - Sexism and media--Sexist music, 1973-1991 (Box 44)
  - Sexism and media--Technical--Animation, 1975 and undated (Box 44)
  - Sexism and media--Technical--Articles, 1971-1974 and undated (Box 44)
  - Sexism and media--Technical--Equipment instructions, undated (Box 44)
  - Sexism and media--Technical--Film, 1970-1976 (Box 44)
  - Sexism and media--Technical--Filmmaking, 1970-1976 (Box 44)
  - Sexism and media--Technical--Glossaries, undated (Box 44)
  - Sexism and media--Technical--Screenwriting, 1977 and undated (Box 44)
  - Sexism and media--Technical--Still photography, 1970-1978 (Box 44)
  - Sexism and media--Technical--Visual materials passed around in the classroom (includes animation flip-books), 1971-1976 and undated (Box 44)
  - Sexism and media--Technical--Voice-overs, 1986 (Box 45)
  - Sexism and media--Video games, 1993 (Box 45)
  - Sexual health--Abortion, 1978-1990 (Box 45)
  - Sexual health--Birth control and sterilization, 1977-1979 (Box 45)
  - Sexual health--DES/Toxic shock syndrome, 1979-1986 (Box 45)
  - Sexual health--Genital mutilation, 1980 (Box 45)
  - Sexual health--Male sexuality, 1978-1982 (Box 45)
  - Sexual health--Teen sexuality and pregnancy, 1981-1991 (Box 45)
  - Sexual images of children, 1983-1995 (Box 45)
  - Soft drinks, 1979-1991 (Box 45)
  - Sugar and sugar substitutes, 1982-1984 (Box 45)
  - Targeting--Elderly, 1979-1980 (Box 45)
  - Targeting--Gays, 1980-1998 (Box 45)
  - Targeting--Middle age, 1979-1981 (Box 45)
  - Targeting--Youth, 1980-1995 (Box 45)
  - Television--As addiction, 1979-1990 (Box 45)
  - Television--Cartoons, 1988 and undated (Box 45)
  - Television--Children, 1974-1997; 2 folders (Box 45)
  - Television--Criticism, 1977-1993 (Box 46)
  - Television--Educational, 1980-2003 (Box 46)
  - Television--Effects, 1978-1984 (Box 46)
  - Television--Minority children, 1978 and undated (Box 46)
  - Television--News, 1982-1995 (Box 46)
  - Television--Public, 1997 (Box 46)
  - Television--Resources, 1978-1988 (Box 46)
  - Television--Statistics, 1985 and undated (Box 46)
  - Television--Stereotypes, 1982-1990 (Box 46)
  - Television--Violence, 1976-1996 (Box 46)
  - The Sexual Sell--Examples, 1979-1993 (Box 46)
  - The Sexual Sell--General, 1978-1994 (Box 46)
  - The Sexual Sell--Protests, 1979-1990 (Box 46)
  - The Sexual Sell--Research studies, 1972-1978 (Box 46)
  - The Sexual Sell--Sexual attitudes, 1971-1982 (Box 46)
  - The Sexual Sell--Theory and criticism, 1973-1991 (Box 46)
  - Tobacco--Addiction, 1980-1997 (Box 47)
  - Tobacco--Advertising bans, 1980-1995 (Box 47)
  - Tobacco--Advertising campaigns, 1997-1998 (Box 47)
  - Tobacco--Advertising criticism, 1975-1992 (Box 47)
  - Tobacco--Advertising effects, 1985-1998 (Box 47)
  - Tobacco--Advertising statistics, 1994-1997 (Box 47)
  - Tobacco--Anti-smoking movement, 1983-1992 (Box 47)
  - Tobacco--Anti-tobacco ads, 1990-1995 (Box 47)
  - Tobacco--Articles and clippings (see also Ch. 8 of book), 1990-2000; 3 folders (Box 47)
  - Tobacco--Children--Joe Camel, 1992-1997 (Box 48)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes--Advertising, 1979-1994 (Box 48)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes--Advertising and women, 1971-1990 (Box 48)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes--Advertising history, 1988 (Box 48)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes--Children, 1992-1999 (Box 48)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes--Dakota, 1990 (Box 48)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes--Health, 1979-1994 (Box 48)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes--Ingredients, 1994 (Box 48)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes--Low-tar, 1977-1994 (Box 48)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes--Marlboro, 1979-1995 (Box 48)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes--Women, 1989-1994 (Box 48)
  - Tobacco--Cigarettes--Women's liberation, 1980 and undated (Box 48)
  - Tobacco--Cigars, 1996-1999 (Box 48)
  - Tobacco--"Covering Tobacco", 1995 (Box 48)
  - Tobacco--Critics within the industry, 1988-1995 (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--Ethical issues, 1983-1994 (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--General, 1976-1996 (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--"Health nazi" rants, 1997-1998 (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--Juvenile smoking, 1986-1995 (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--Madvertising (Ventura County Tobacco Education and Prevention Coalition), undated (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--Minorities and global, 1995-1999 (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--Nonsmokers' rights, 1988-1992 (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--Parodies of ads, 1976-1995 (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--Politics, 1983-1998 (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--Prevention ads, 1983 and undated (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--Quitting, 1978-1993 (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--Quitting and gender, 1989-1996 (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--Settlement, 1997-1999 (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--Sexuality, 1986-1995 (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--Smoke and Mirrors (Advocacy group publication), 1998 (Box 49)
  - Tobacco--Smokeless, 1985-1996 (Box 50)
  - Tobacco--Smokers' rights, 1981-1995 (Box 50)
  - Tobacco--Women--Historical timeline, undated (Box 51)
  - Tobacco--Smoking and women, 1985-1995 (Box 50)
  - Tobacco--Smoking criticism, 1985-1994 (Box 50)
  - Tobacco--Stress, depression, etc., 1981-1999 (Box 50)
  - Tobacco--Targeting minorities, 1986-1997 (Box 50)
  - Tobacco--Targeting youth, 1986-1995 (Box 50)
  - Tobacco--Third World use, 1980-1997 (Box 50)
  - Tobacco--Tobacco Biology and Politics (Stanton Glantz), 1992 (Box 50)
  - Tobacco--Tobacco industry, 1984-1999; 2 folders (Box 50)
  - Tobacco--Tobacco industry employment, 1993-1996 (Box 50)
  - Tobacco--Tobacco industry public relations, 1981-1995 (Box 50)
  - Tobacco--Warnings, 1980-1995 (Box 51)
  - Tobacco--Women, 1986-1998 (Box 51)
  - Tobacco--Women--Challenging the Allure of Smoking (Mass. Dept. of Public Health), 1998 (Box 51)
  - Tobacco--Women--Cigarettes, 1977-1995 (Box 51)
  - Tobacco--Women--Food and weight control, 1982-1995 (Box 51)
  - Tobacco--Women--International Network of Women Against Tobacco, 2001 (Box 51)
  - Tobacco--Women--Survey of Design Concepts Motivating Women Smokers (Anna Lafferty, MFA thesis), 1980; 2 folders (Box 51)
  - Violence--Battering, 1979-1994 (Box 51)
  - Violence--Battering research, 1979-1993; 2 folders (Box 52)
  - Violence--Child abuse, 1978-1995 (Box 52)
  - Violence--Child sexual abuse, 1973-1994 (Box 52)
  - Violence--Emerge (a counseling company), 1979-1981 (Box 52)
  - Violence--General, 1977-1994 (Box 52)
  - Violence--Incest, 1978-1992 (Box 52)
  - Violence--Incest--Voices (an advocacy organization), 1985 and undated (Box 53)
  - Violence--Mass. Coalition of Battered Women, 1981 (Box 53)
  - Violence--National Coalition Against Domestic Violence, undated (Box 53)
  - Violence--National Family Life, 1985 and undated (Box 53)
  - Violence--O.J. Simpson, 1994 (Box 53)
  - Violence--Prostitution and sexual slavery, 1979-1980 (Box 53)
  - Violence--Rape--Date rape, 1982-1993 (Box 53)
  - Violence--Rape--Feminist theory, 1976-1993 (Box 53)
  - Violence--Rape--General, 1977-1990 (Box 53)
  - Violence--Rape--Popular media, 1977-1994 (Box 53)
  - Violence--Research, 1970-1990 (Box 53)
  - Violence--Self-defense, 1978-1993 (Box 53)
  - Violence--Sexual harassment, 1977-1991 (Box 53)
  - Violence--Women Against Violence Against Women (WAVAW), 1977-1979 (Box 53)
  - Violence--Women Against Violence in Pornography and Media, 1977 (Box 53)
  - Women--Art and music, 1977-1982 (Box 53)
  - Women--Cross-cultural, 1976-1992 (Box 54)
  - Women--Equal Rights Amendment, 1976 (Box 54)
  - Women--In advertising, 1975-1996; 2 folders (Box 54)
  - Women--In government, 1984 and undated (Box 54)
  - Women--Legal system, 1977-1978 (Box 54)
  - Women--Literature, 1973-1981 (Box 54)
- Teaching Files, 1969-1993 and undated; 12 boxes
  - Action and protest, 1979-1993 (Box 54)
  - Activities and puzzles, 1970-1980 (Box 54)
  - Anthropology, 1973-1979 (Box 54)
  - Anthropology--Book notes, questions, etc., undated (Box 54)
  - Biased textbooks (Weitzman & Rizzo), 1974 (Box 54)
  - Body language, 1970-1978 (Box 54)
  - Boston Area Teaching Project, 1968 (Box 54)
  - Boston University--African American studies resources, 1969-1972 (Box 55)
  - Boston University--Blues and Soul course, 1969 (Box 55)
  - Boston University--Buddhism and Eastern Thought, 1971-1972 (Box 55)
  - Boston University--Comics and comedy, 1969 and undated (Box 55)
  - Boston University--Course unit proposals, 1965-1969 (Box 55)
  - Boston University--Critical thinking, 1969-1975 (Box 55)
  - Boston University--Drama, undated (Box 55)
  - Boston University--Education and Moral Development (HB526), 1965-1976 (Box 55)
  - Boston University--Race relations articles, 1969-1970 (Box 55)
  - Boston University--Race relations course, 1968-1969 (Box 55)
  - Boston University--Speech and linguistics, 1965-1970 (Box 56)
  - Bradford College, 1976-1977 (Box 56)
  - Carlos Castaneda/Don Juan, 1977 (Box 56)
  - Children, Youth and Family Life (Kaufman, Schmuck, Lippitt), 1963 (Box 56)
  - Communication--Articles, notes, etc., 1970-1976 (Box 56)
  - Communication theory, undated (Box 56)
  - Creative writing--Articles and miscellaneous, 1965 and undated (Box 56)
  - Creative writing--Assignments, 1969 and undated (Box 56)
  - Creative writing--Dialogue, 1972 and undated (Box 56)
  - Creative writing--Mimeo masters, undated (Box 56)
  - Creative writing--Miscellaneous, undated (Box 56)
  - Creative writing--Photographs, postcards, etc., undated (Box 56)
  - Creative writing--Resources--Making It Strange, 1968 (Box 56)
  - Creative writing--Resources--Making It Strange, 1968 (Box 57)
  - Creative writing--Resources--Miscellaneous, undated (Box 57)
  - Creative writing--Sensory awareness articles, 1969 and undated (Box 57)
  - Creative writing--Sensory awareness ideas, exercises, undated (Box 57)
  - Creative writing and communication, 1965-1974 (Box 57)
  - Creative writing and self-awareness, 1966-1977 (Box 57)
  - Ecology and population, 1969-1981 (Box 57)
  - Education--Articles, 1967-1979 (Box 57)
  - Education--Articles, notes, etc., 1969-1972 (Box 57)
  - Education--Miscellaneous, 1969-1976 (Box 57)
  - Effects of media violence, 1984-1994 (Box 58)
  - Emerson College--Barbara Epstein materials (poetry course), undated (Box 58)
  - Emerson College--Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 58)
  - Emerson College--ED365 methods and materials, 1975 (Box 58)
  - Emerson College--Electric Media (Ward & Hardesty), 1973 (Box 58)
  - Emerson College--Escape from Freedom (Erich Fromm), 1974 (Box 58)
  - Emerson College--First Level Program, 1973-1975; 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Emerson College--First Level Program--Getting acquainted excercise/paper and self-evaluation papers, 1974 (Box 58)
  - Emerson College--First Level Program--Student Report on FLP Status, 1973 (Box 58)
  - Emerson College--General assignments and activities, 1970-1977 (Box 58)
  - Emerson College--Miscellaneous clippings, notes, etc., 1965-1973 (Box 58)
  - Emerson College--Seminar, 1973-1974 (Box 58)
  - Emerson College--Student papers, 1973-1974; 2 folders (Box 59)
  - Emerson College--Term I, 1972-1974; 6 folders (Box 59)
  - Emerson College--Term II, 1974-1975 and undated; 3 folders (Box 59)
  - Emerson College--Units and handouts, 1969-1973 (Box 59)
  - Film study course--Articles, 1969-1977 (Box 59)
  - Film study course--Articles about filmmakers, 1970-1977 (Box 59)
  - Film study course--Articles on film criticism and analysis, 1974-1976 (Box 59)
  - Film study course--Bibliographies, 1969-1973 (Box 59)
  - Film study course--Curricula, etc., 1965-1973 (Box 60)
  - Film study course--Discussions, film language, etc., 1969-1972 (Box 60)
  - Film study course--Film and fiction, 1973 and undated (Box 60)
  - Film study course--Film guides, undated; 2 folders (Box 60)
  - Film study course--Film information and ideas, 1974 (Box 60)
  - Film study course--Filmmaking activities and assignments, 1970-1975 (Box 60)
  - Film study course--Information about my students' films, undated (Box 60)
  - Film study course--My film course, undated (Box 60)
  - Film study course--Rationale, 1967-1976; 2 folders (Box 60)
  - Film study course--Reviews and notes, 1973 and undated (Box 61)
  - Film study course--Specific film units, 1970 and undated (Box 61)
  - Film study course--Workshop, undated (Box 61)
  - Free-lance writing, 1968 (Box 61)
  - Free-lance writing--London School of Journalism course, undated; 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Games--including MadLibs, Felt Smelt (Warren Dayton), undated (Box 61)
  - Crading and evaluation, 1973 (Box 61)
  - Group process, 1979 and undated (Box 61)
  - Group process--Exercises, 1964-1971 (Box 61)
  - Guidelines, 1975-1979 and undated (Box 61)
  - Inspirational quotes, undated (Box 61)
  - Interpersonal communications, undated (Box 61)
  - List of films used in my courses, 1971-1974 (Box 61)
  - Media--Comics, 1969-1977 (Box 61)
  - Media--Photography contest and career information, 1968-1973 (Box 61)
  - Media--Photojournalism, undated (Box 61)
  - Media--Radio, 1976-1977 (Box 61)
  - Media course 1-A, 1969 (Box 62)
  - Mimeograph masters, undated (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous articles, 1970-1974 (Box 62)
  - Nonverbal communication, 1968 and undated (Box 62)
  - Norms, undated (Box 62)
  - Norwall High School--Creative writing, 1969 (Box 62)
  - Norwall High School--English 11--Brave New World, 1969-1970 (Box 62)
  - Norwall High School--English 11--Notes, undated (Box 62)
  - Norwall High School--English 30/31 final examinations, undated (Box 62)
  - Norwall High School--English 31--1984, 1969-1970 (Box 62)
  - Norwall High School--Literature of Protest--Articles, 1969-1972 (Box 62)
  - Norwall High School--Literature of Protest--Notes, etc., 1971 (Box 62)
  - Norwall High School--Literature of Protest--Student evaluations, 1971 (Box 62)
  - Norwall High School--Poetry examples, undated (Box 62)
  - Norwall High School--Political mini-courses, 1972 (Box 62)
  - Norwall High School--Portrait of the Artist (James Joyce), 1961-1970 (Box 63)
  - Norwall High School--Rose Garden, 1969-1976 (Box 63)
  - Norwall High School--Rose Garden--Schizophrenia articles and poems, undated (Box 63)
  - Norwall High School--Stereotypes of Native Americans, 1971-1980 (Box 63)
  - Norwall High School--Student correspondence, 1972 (Box 63)
  - Norwall High School--Unit on war, 1969-1972 (Box 63)
  - Norwall High School--Using media creatively in the classroom, 1975 (Box 63)
  - Norwall High School--Words and language, 1969-1973 (Box 63)
  - Norwall High School--Writng style and point of view, 1965 and undated (Box 63)
  - Observation and feedback, undated (Box 63)
  - Poetry--Articles and resources, 1966-1973 (Box 63)
  - Poetry--Black poets, 1969 and undated (Box 63)
  - Poetry--Chinese (Brian Powell), undated (Box 63)
  - Poetry--Contemporary, 1971 (Box 64)
  - Poetry--Loneliness, undated (Box 64)
  - Poetry--Love, undated (Box 64)
  - Poetry--Poetry writing, undated (Box 64)
  - Poetry--Protest, undated (Box 64)